<rooms>
    <room>
        <id>1</id>
        <roomName>key room</roomName>
        <roomExits>
            <exit>
                <path>east</path>
                <pathName>library</pathName>
                <lockKey>scholar's key</lockKey>
                <lockMessage>You unlock the door to the library and enter.</lockMessage>
                <commandInt>2</commandInt>
            </exit>
            <exit>
                <path>north</path>
                <pathName>swinging stairs</pathName>
            </exit>
            <exit>
                <path>south</path>
                <pathName>kitchen</pathName>
            </exit>
            <exit>
                <path>west</path>
                <pathName>psych ward</pathName>
            </exit>
        </roomExits>
        <roomDescription>Four bare walls keep you as a prisoner to an overly bright room with no windows. Shelves with millions of keys in varying sizes, shapes, and colors line the floors like passageways to four doors around you. What lies behind each door is unknown to you, but your options are limited. Faded, and somewhat unclear to read above the east side door reads "libra". The keys you touch are as real as the keys to your home, varying in shapes and sizes.
        </roomDescription>
    </room>
    <room>
        <id>2</id>
        <roomName>library</roomName>
        <roomExits>
            <exit>
                <path>north</path>
                <pathName>loud room</pathName>
            </exit>
            <exit>
                <path>south</path>
                <pathName>creaky path</pathName>
            </exit>
            <exit>
                <path>west</path>
                <pathName>key room</pathName>
            </exit>
        </roomExits>
        <roomDescription>An overly large room with cobwebbed filled shelves, over sized portraits with headless bodies, and open skylights. Under the full moon night, a single locked chest is highlighted on the perfectly centered table. Surrounding the table, a thin line of salt surrounds the only seemingly normal thing in the room.
        </roomDescription>
    </room>
    <room>
        <id>3</id>
        <roomName>loud room</roomName>
        <roomExits>
            <exit>
                <path>east</path>
                <pathName>engraving cave</pathName>
            </exit>
            <exit>
                <path>south</path>
                <pathName>library</pathName>
            </exit>
        </roomExits>
        <roomDescription>As if you have entered a Kiss concert, music blares against your ears. On all corners of the room, speakers climb the cathedral ceilings, vibrating waves through the room.
        </roomDescription>
    </room>
    <room>
        <id>4</id>
        <roomName>psych ward</roomName>
        <roomExits>
            <exit>
                <path>east</path>
                <pathName>key room</pathName>
            </exit>
            <exit>
                <path>south</path>
                <pathName>closet</pathName>
            </exit>
        </roomExits>
        <roomDescription>Lined along the walls are metal framed beds, plain with white sheets and drapes hanging over them. Dolls with cracked and fractured faces sit at the end of each bed, following you as you move around the room. From beneath the beds, a chill crawls up your legs, up your back, and around the sides of your neck.
        </roomDescription>
    </room>
    <room>
        <id>5</id>
        <roomName>kitchen</roomName>
        <roomExits>
            <exit>
                <path>north</path>
                <pathName>key room</pathName>
            </exit>
        </roomExits>
        <roomDescription>Like darts, knives hang from the vaulted ceiling in varying sizes. Across the white marble island, an oven blasts heat in your direction, carrying the smell of blackened cookies. As if the walls were made of paper, conversations can be heard in the other room.
        </roomDescription>
    </room>
    <room>
        <id>6</id>
        <roomName>creaky path</roomName>
        <roomExits>
            <exit>
                <path>north</path>
                <pathName>library</pathName>
            </exit>
            <exit>
                <path>east</path>
                <pathName>coal mine</pathName>
            </exit>
        </roomExits>
        <roomDescription>Above a bed of rocks with crashing waters, a wooden bridge cries in the wind. Bundled in a wicker basket, rope is tangled around itself, rendering itself nearly useless.
        </roomDescription>
    </room>
    <room>
        <id>7</id>
        <roomName>coal mine</roomName>
        <roomExits>
            <exit>
                <path>west</path>
                <pathName>creaky path</pathName>
            </exit>
        </roomExits>
        <roomDescription>Dimly lit lamps, covered in soot, line the walls of the mine down a path cut short by tumbled rock. An old pickaxe lays against the wall, next to a faded, brown miners hat and a gas mask.
        </roomDescription>
    </room>
    <room>
        <id>8</id>
        <roomName>secret passage</roomName>
        <roomExits>
            <exit>
                <path>north</path>
                <pathName>kitchen</pathName>
            </exit>
        </roomExits>
        <roomDescription>Long and narrow before you, an empty passage shows a single door at the opposite end.
        </roomDescription>
    </room>
    <room>
        <id>9</id>
        <roomName>volcano</roomName>
        <roomExits>
            <exit>
                <path>east</path>
                <pathName>secret passage</pathName>
            </exit>
        </roomExits>
        <roomDescription>Spewing lava from it's top, a volcano destroys everything near it. A random, small door stands alone at the edge of the treeline, only twenty feet from a lava river.
        </roomDescription>
    </room>
    <room>
        <id>10</id>
        <roomName>treasure room</roomName>
        <roomExits>
            <exit>
                <path>west</path>
                <pathName>river</pathName>
                <lockKey>magic cape</lockKey>
                <lockMessage>With your magic cape, you carry yourself through the air, west across the river.
                </lockMessage>
                <commandInt>2</commandInt>
            </exit>
            <exit>
                <path>south</path>
                <pathName>volcano</pathName>
            </exit>
        </roomExits>
        <roomDescription>Piles upon piles of gold and gems climb to the sky, high where birds fly. A platinum river, boiling at over 3,000 degrees, flows through the middle of a reflective meadow. For miles west, the river appears to never end.
        </roomDescription>
    </room>
    <room>
        <id>11</id>
        <roomName>riddle room</roomName>
        <roomExits>
            <exit>
                <path>east</path>
                <pathName>closet</pathName>
            </exit>
            <exit>
                <path>west</path>
                <pathName>whispering passage</pathName>
            </exit>
        </roomExits>
        <roomDescription>The empty room bares a tulip filled wallpaper with a single portion ripped away to reveal a riddle.
        </roomDescription>
    </room>
    <room>
        <id>12</id>
        <roomName>whispering passage</roomName>
        <roomExits>
            <exit>
                <path>west</path>
                <pathName>treasure room</pathName>
            </exit>
        </roomExits>
        <roomDescription>With each step you take down the cobblestone path, a footstep behind you can be heard. Whispers in your ear sound as if someone is right behind you, but upon turning around, no one is there. In the center of the path is a rotted bench with fresh flowers and a photograph.
        </roomDescription>
    </room>
    <room>
        <id>13</id>
        <roomName>closet</roomName>
        <roomExits>
            <exit>
                <path>north</path>
                <pathName>psych ward</pathName>
            </exit>
            <exit>
                <path>west</path>
                <pathName>riddle room</pathName>
            </exit>
        </roomExits>
        <roomDescription>A single light dimly guides you through a small space. Packed tight with clothes from eras that don't make sense to one another, you struggle to push your way through. Several boxes lay atop the shelves, covered in dust.
        </roomDescription>
    </room>
    <room>
        <id>14</id>
        <roomName>swinging stairs</roomName>
        <roomExits>
            <exit>
                <path>north</path>
                <pathName>egyptian room</pathName>
            </exit>
            <exit>
                <path>south</path>
                <pathName>key room</pathName>
            </exit>
        </roomExits>
        <roomDescription>From left to right, staircases move around you, loud and reckless, clashing against walls like thunder. Below seems to be an endless pit with cries and blazing heat lifting high in the room.
        </roomDescription>
    </room>
    <room>
        <id>15</id>
        <roomName>egyptian room</roomName>
        <roomExits>
            <exit>
                <path>east</path>
                <pathName>land of the dead</pathName>
                <lockKey>skeleton key</lockKey>
                <lockMessage>You use the skeleton key to unlock the door to the land of the dead.</lockMessage>
                <commandInt>2</commandInt>
            </exit>
            <exit>
                <path>west</path>
                <pathName>art room</pathName>
                <lockKey>sculpture</lockKey>
                <lockMessage>With defeating this monster, dark energy starts to spew from the art room.</lockMessage>
                <commandInt>2</commandInt>
            </exit>
            <exit>
                <path>south</path>
                <pathName>swinging stairs</pathName>
            </exit>
        </roomExits>
        <roomDescription>As you step through the door, sand brushes across your face, forcing your eyes to veer to upward. You are now in the desert with pyramids and camels before you. Like the door behind you, there are two other doors that are situated in the middle of the dessert, attached to nothing.
        </roomDescription>
    </room>
    <room>
        <id>16</id>
        <roomName>land of the dead</roomName>
        <roomExits>
            <exit>
                <path>west</path>
                <pathName>egyptian room</pathName>
            </exit>
        </roomExits>
        <roomDescription>With every step, your feet slush through murky water. Willow branches hang low above you, blocking clear sight of an exit. Fog lifts from the top of the water, further blocking your view, the stinch of death seeping through your nose hairs.
        </roomDescription>
    </room>
    <room>
        <id>17</id>
        <roomName>art room</roomName>
        <roomExits>
            <exit>
                <path>east</path>
                <pathName>egyptian room</pathName>
            </exit>
        </roomExits>
        <roomDescription>Fumes of alcohol fill the air as moisture drips down the paintings on easels, almost as if the subjects are crying themselves. A red liquid covers the floor, not dry, nor wet. In the center of the room, a sculpture is covered with a cloth, the same red liquid coming from the bottom.
        </roomDescription>
    </room>
    <room>
        <id>18</id>
        <roomName>engraving cave</roomName>
        <roomExits>
            <exit>
                <path>north</path>
                <pathName>floating room</pathName>
            </exit>
            <exit>
                <path>west</path>
                <pathName>loud room</pathName>
            </exit>
        </roomExits>
        <roomDescription>Musty air carries you through a tombstone filled cave, scratches covering the walls, random but deep. A narrow passage sucks air from the cave, making it harder to breathe by the second.
        </roomDescription>
    </room>
    <room>
        <id>19</id>
        <roomName>floating room</roomName>
        <roomExits>
            <exit>
                <path>west</path>
                <pathName>land of the dead</pathName>
            </exit>
        </roomExits>
        <roomDescription>Heavy as a boulder, standing on a feather, your foot triggers a pressure plate on the floor. Large bubbles burst of cotton candy around you, one of them surrounding you and lifting you to the ceiling.
        </roomDescription>
    </room>
    <room>
        <id>20</id>
        <roomName>river</roomName>
        <roomExits>
            <exit>
                <path>east</path>
                <pathName>treasure room</pathName>
                <lockKey>magic cape</lockKey>
                <lockMessage>With your magic cape, you carry yourself through the air, east across the river.
                </lockMessage>
                <commandInt>2</commandInt>
            </exit>
        </roomExits>
        <roomDescription>Miles upon miles of darkness and emptiness surrounds a platinum river with a shine that could light an entire city. Bubbles burst around you at high temperatures as you fly with your magic cape. The sight of a single pedestal stops you from going farther.
        </roomDescription>
    </room>
</rooms>


        <!--        Heat radiates from an oversized fireplace with stockings hanging dangerously too close to flames, likely causing the extra singed aroma.-->
        <!--        An old night stand features a stack of books that could compete with the Leaning Tower of Pisa.-->
        <!--        Across the room, a portrait of a man with knotted hair, fractured glasses, and a twisted smile, stares in your direction.-->