<rooms>
    <room>
        <id>1</id>
        <roomName>living</roomName>
        <roomExits>
            <exit>
                <path>north</path>
                <pathName>swingingStairs</pathName>
            </exit>
            <exit>
                <path>east</path>
                <pathName>library</pathName>
            </exit>
            <exit>
                <path>south</path>
                <pathName>kitchen</pathName>
            </exit>
            <exit>
                <path>west</path>
                <pathName>bedroom</pathName>
            </exit>
        </roomExits>
        <items>
            <item>candle</item>
            <item>test</item>
        </items>
        <roomDescription>
            Heat radiates from an oversized fireplace with stockings hanging dangerously too close to flames, likely causing the extra singed aroma.
            An old night stand features a stack of books that could compete with the Leaning Tower of Pisa.
            Across the room, a portrait of a man with knotted hair, fractured glasses, and a twisted smile, stares in your exit.
        </roomDescription>
    </room>
    <room>
        <id>2</id>
        <roomName>library</roomName>
        <roomExits>
            <exit>
                <path>north</path>
                <pathName>loudRoom</pathName>
            </exit>
            <exit>
                <path>south</path>
                <pathName>creekyPath</pathName>
            </exit>
            <exit>
                <path>west</path>
                <pathName>living</pathName>
            </exit>
        </roomExits>
        <items>
        </items>
        <roomDescription>
            With cobwebbed filled shelves, oversized portraits with headless bodies, and open skylights add an extra hill of mystery to the room.
            Under the full moon night, a single locked chest is highlighted on the perfectly centered table.
            Surrounding the table, a thin line of salt surrounds the only seemingly normal thing in the room.
        </roomDescription>
    </room>
    <room>
        <id>3</id>
        <roomName>loudRoom</roomName>
        <roomExits>
            <exit>
                <path>east</path>
                <pathName>engravingCave</pathName>
            </exit>
            <exit>
                <path>south</path>
                <pathName>library</pathName>
            </exit>
        </roomExits>
        <items>
        </items>
        <roomDescription>
            As if you have entered a Kiss concert, music blares against your ears.
            On all corners of the room, speakers climb the cathedral ceilings, vibrating waves through the room.
            From atop of the farthest speaker, a shiny object glimmers in the changing colors of the neon lights.
        </roomDescription>
    </room>
    <room>
        <id>4</id>
        <roomName>bedroom</roomName>
        <roomExits>
            <exit>
                <path>east</path>
                <pathName>living</pathName>
            </exit>
            <exit>
                <path>south</path>
                <pathName>closet</pathName>
            </exit>
        </roomExits>
        <items>
        </items>
        <roomDescription>
            An unmade child's bed sits in the center of the room, the foot of the bed facing the wall.
            Several dolls with cracked and fractured faces, follow you as you move around the room.
            From beneath the bed, a chill crawls up your legs, up your back, and around the sides of your neck.
        </roomDescription>
    </room>
    <room>
        <id>5</id>
        <roomName>kitchen</roomName>
        <roomExits>
            <exit>
                <path>north</path>
                <pathName>living</pathName>
            </exit>
        </roomExits>
        <items>
        </items>
        <roomDescription>
            Like darts, knives hang from the vaulted ceiling in varying sizes.
            Across the white marble island, an oven blasts heat in your exit, carrying the smell of blackened cookies.
            As if the walls were made of paper, conversations can be heard in the other room.
        </roomDescription>
    </room>
    <room>
        <id>6</id>
        <roomName>creekyPath</roomName>
        <roomExits>
            <exit>
                <path>north</path>
                <pathName>library</pathName>
            </exit>
            <exit>
                <path>east</path>
                <pathName>coalMine</pathName>
            </exit>
        </roomExits>
        <items>
        </items>
        <roomDescription>
            Above a bed of rocks with crashing waters, a wooden bridge cries in the wind.
            Bundled in a wicker basket, rope is tangled around itself, rendering itself nearly useless.
        </roomDescription>
    </room>
    <room>
        <id>7</id>
        <roomName>coalMine</roomName>
        <roomExits>
            <exit>
                <path>west</path>
                <pathName>creekyPath</pathName>
            </exit>
        </roomExits>
        <items>
        </items>
        <roomDescription>
            Dimly lit lamps, covered in soot, line the walls of the mine down a path cut short by tumbled rock.
            An old pickaxe lays against the wall, next to a faded, yellow hat and a gas mask.
        </roomDescription>
    </room>
    <room>
        <id>8</id>
        <roomName>secretPassage</roomName>
        <roomExits>
            <exit>
                <path>north</path>
                <pathName>kitchen</pathName>
            </exit>
        </roomExits>
        <items>
        </items>
        <roomDescription>
            Long and narrow before you, an empty passage shows a single door at the opposite end.
        </roomDescription>
    </room>
    <room>
        <id>9</id>
        <roomName>torchRoom</roomName>
        <roomExits>
            <exit>
                <path>east</path>
                <pathName>secretPassage</pathName>
            </exit>
        </roomExits>
        <items>
        </items>
        <roomDescription>
            Tiki torches line a maze through the room.
            In the center of the room is an in-ground hot tub filled with lava, bubbling over the sides.
        </roomDescription>
    </room>
    <room>
        <id>10</id>
        <roomName>treasureRoom</roomName>
        <roomExits>
            <exit>
                <path>south</path>
                <pathName>torchRoom</pathName>
            </exit>
        </roomExits>
        <items>
            <item>key</item>
        </items>
        <roomDescription>
            Piles upon piles of gold and gems climb to the top of the room, surrounding a platinum river flowing through the middle.
            A single lizard shaped key stands on a single pedestal in the center of the river.
        </roomDescription>
    </room>
    <room>
        <id>11</id>
        <roomName>riddleRoom</roomName>
        <roomExits>
            <exit>
                <path>east</path>
                <pathName>closet</pathName>
            </exit>
            <exit>
                <path>west</path>
                <pathName>whisperingPassage</pathName>
            </exit>
        </roomExits>
        <items>
        </items>
        <roomDescription>
            The empty room bares a tulip filled wallpaper with a single portion ripped away to reveal a riddle.
            With gold shining high in the sky, a bird cannot soar if it cannot fly.
            A stream that flows is a life to grow, a stream not of water may death undergo.
            Unlocking a secret is not a forfeit, go forward with the lizard to be rewarded.
        </roomDescription>
    </room>
    <room>
        <id>12</id>
        <roomName>whisperingPassage</roomName>
        <roomExits>
            <exit>
                <path>west</path>
                <pathName>treasureRoom</pathName>
            </exit>
        </roomExits>
        <items>
        </items>
        <roomDescription>
            With each step you take down the cobblestone path, a footstep behind you can be heard.
            Whispers in your ear sound as if someone is right behind you, but upon turning around, no one is there.
            In the center of the path is a rotted bench with fresh flowers and a photograph.
        </roomDescription>
    </room>
    <room>
        <id>13</id>
        <roomName>closet</roomName>
        <roomExits>
            <exit>
                <path>north</path>
                <pathName>bedroom</pathName>
            </exit>
            <exit>
                <path>west</path>
                <pathName>riddleRoom</pathName>
            </exit>
        </roomExits>
        <items>
            <item>match</item>
        </items>
        <roomDescription>
            A single light dimly guides you through a small space.
            Packed tight with clothes from eras that don't make sense to one another, you struggle to push your way through.
            Several shoe boxes lay atop the shelves, covered in dust.
        </roomDescription>
    </room>
    <room>
        <id>14</id>
        <roomName>swingingStairs</roomName>
        <roomExits>
            <exit>
                <path>north</path>
                <pathName>egyptianRoom</pathName>
            </exit>
            <exit>
                <path>south</path>
                <pathName>living</pathName>
            </exit>
        </roomExits>
        <items>
        </items>
        <roomDescription>
            From left to right, staircases move around you, loud and reckless, clashing against walls like thunder.
            Below seems to be an endless pit with cries and blazing heat lifting high in the room.
        </roomDescription>
    </room>
    <room>
        <id>15</id>
        <roomName>egyptianRoom</roomName>
        <roomExits>
            <exit>
                <path>east</path>
                <pathName>landOfDead</pathName>
            </exit>
            <exit>
                <path>south</path>
                <pathName>living</pathName>
            </exit>
            <exit>
                <path>west</path>
                <pathName>artRoom</pathName>
            </exit>
        </roomExits>
        <items>
        </items>
        <roomDescription>
            As you step through the door, sand brushes across your face, forcing your eyes to veer to upward.
            You are now in the desert with pyramids and camels before you.
        </roomDescription>
    </room>
    <room>
        <id>16</id>
        <roomName>landOfDead</roomName>
        <roomExits>
            <exit>
                <path>west</path>
                <pathName>egyptianRoom</pathName>
            </exit>
        </roomExits>
        <items>
        </items>
        <roomDescription>
            With every step, your feet slush through murky water. Willow branches hang low above you, blocking clear sight of an exit.
            Fog lifts from the top of the water, further blocking your view, the stinch of death seeping through your nose hairs.
        </roomDescription>
    </room>
    <room>
        <id>17</id>
        <roomName>artRoom</roomName>
        <roomExits>
            <exit>
                <path>east</path>
                <pathName>egyptianRoom</pathName>
            </exit>
        </roomExits>
        <items>
        </items>
        <roomDescription>
            Fumes of alcohol fill the air as moisture drips down the paintings on easels, almost as if the subjects are crying themselves.
            A red liquid covers the floor, not dry, nor wet.
            In the center of the room, a sculpture is covered with a cloth, the same red liquid coming from the bottom.
        </roomDescription>
    </room>
    <room>
        <id>18</id>
        <roomName>engravingCave</roomName>
        <roomExits>
            <exit>
                <path>north</path>
                <pathName>floatingRoom</pathName>
            </exit>
            <exit>
                <path>west</path>
                <pathName>loudRoom</pathName>
            </exit>
        </roomExits>
        <items>
        </items>
        <roomDescription>
            Musty air carries you through a tombstone filled cave, scratches covering the walls, random but deep.
            A narrow passage sucks air from the cave, making it harder to breathe by the second.
        </roomDescription>
    </room>
    <room>
        <id>19</id>
        <roomName>floatingRoom</roomName>
        <roomExits>
            <exit>
                <path>west</path>
                <pathName>landOfDead</pathName>
            </exit>
        </roomExits>
        <items>
        </items>
        <roomDescription>
            Heavy as a boulder, standing on a feather, your foot triggers a pressure plate on the floor.
            Large bubbles burst of cotton candy around you, one of them surrounding you and lifting you to the ceiling.
        </roomDescription>
    </room>
</rooms>